<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<staticContent id="85" tag="frontPage" published="1"><parentContent/><siblingContent><content id="80"><title><![CDATA[Termeni de utilizare]]></title></content><content id="81"><title><![CDATA[Politica de confidentialitate]]></title></content><content id="83"><title><![CDATA[Error 404 Not found]]></title></content><content id="84"><title><![CDATA[Error 500 Internal Server Error]]></title></content><content id="86"><title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title></content><content id="87"><title><![CDATA[Welcome to the links page]]></title></content></siblingContent><childContent/><content><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to PublicLiabilityInsurance.ie&nbsp; site&nbsp; &ndash; the site for Professionals, Consultants and Tutors&nbsp; seeking Public Liability insurance.</p>
<p>Over our many years in the Insurance Broking business we have seen that many small consultancies and tutors / teachers and Professionals&nbsp; have difficulty arranging simple Public Liability insurance to cover their liability to members of the public arising from their occupation .&nbsp; Buyers want Quick , Instant , Low cost Public Liability insurance for their business.</p>
<p>We have partnered with <a href="http://www.ipr.ie/" target="_blank">WR Berkley</a> Insurance Group to provide the solution to the above &ndash; PublicLiabilityInsurance.ie&nbsp; enables you to buy&nbsp; Liability Insurance at&nbsp; Low Cost and in an Instant and with a quality insurance company.</p>
<p>If you need Public Liability&nbsp; cover then look no further, your public liability insurance search is over, click for an insurance quote!</p>
<p>In addition, for those that require same we can offer Professional Indemnity Insurance, the cover you need to protect your clients&nbsp;&nbsp; from your negligence, oversight or incorrect advice. Previously only available at high minimum premiums- If you are interested in this cover please follow the link to our Professional Indemnity&nbsp; insurance site (www.piinsurance.ie) <br /><br />You can have your Public Liability insurance arranged within minutes&nbsp; &ndash; click on the <br />Quote button below to find out how! Please remember we can also quote for other commercial business not only the ones listed</p>]]></content><title><![CDATA[Welcome to publicLiability.ie]]></title></staticContent>
